♪♪
Joe, I'm certain you know
how difficult it must have been
for Ginny to tell you that your
lovemaking... well, bores her.
Difficult for her?
What about me?
Well, we've made a
real breakthrough here.
Next time, we'll build on it.
Ginny, hug Joe.
Joe, kiss Ginny.
Don't start snoring.
Your humor, Joe, is marvelous.
And Ginny's honesty...
I'm going to have to say you
kids make one heck of a couple.
Now, I know you
probably don't realize this,
but there was an awful
lot of love in this room.
See you at 6?
I'm having a crisis, Doctor.
I need your help.
No, Laura, not
here. Laura, not now.
I checked your book.
You're clear for three hours.
Stop it. Someone might come in.
My place in 20 minutes?
Okay, Ben, here we go...
Your life insurance needs.
Now, are you aware
that your coverage
should provide one to seven
times your annual income?
Uh... Not to mention
your estate liquidity.
Ben, you made a bundle
since my last review.
You're going to need
additional coverage.
But remember, I'm
not selling insurance.
I'm selling peace of mind.
How can you sleep knowing
your assets are uncovered?
I didn't know they were.
Do you have a copy of your parent
policy? We'll go over it line by line.
I might even have one in here.
No, I've got mine.
I've got mine.
You stay here and keep talking.
I think I saw it in
here yesterday.
I was at a seminar
last year when...
Please, dear God,
cut his tongue out.
Let's see if it's in... No, no.
Oh, I know. Here. Here,
here, here. Let's see. Yeah.
Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe.
- Ben, I...
- Yeah.
You want to maximize
your retirement benefits, Ben.
Then there's our new
disability coverage.
Chronic illness and severe injury can
strike men in your age group every day.
With our policy, you can break every bone
in your body... even lose your members.
My members?
Arms, legs... you know.
Members?
Or you can go deaf, dumb,
and blind and get paid for it.
My members?
How's your wife?
Oh, uh, Laura? She's great.
Well, actually, we've
been having a little trouble.
Started seeing a marriage
counselor... Dr. Fletcher. Terrific guy.
He got right to the
heart of the problem.
You see, Ben, Laura needs to
talk about her feelings, and I...
Well, I have trouble
expressing myself.
You do?
Mmm.
Oh, you were wonderful, Harding.
Do you love me?
Can't you tell?
What was that?
- It's Alan.
- Damn.
Harding, the back door.
Laura? Laura?
Honey, are you home?
Honey, aren't you supposed to be
in your group session at the clinic?
Aren't you supposed
to be selling insurance?
Well, I did. Ben Matlock just
bought and bought and bought.
Why aren't you dressed?
I'm showering... now.
What?
Laura?
HF?
HF.
Harding Fletcher?
Laura?
Laura.
- Laura!
- What is it?
Harding Fletcher.
I can explain.
I only tried it once.
You only tried it once?
Tobacco.
Wait. Wait. I'm spending
a fortune on a therapist
so you can try his tobacco?
He's saving our marriage.
He's sleeping with my wife.
Where are you going?
Where a crazy person
goes... To see a shrink.
Fletcher!
- There's somebody in there.
- Huh.
- Fletcher!
- Alan?
You've been
sleeping with my wife.
Alan, what are
you talking about?
You know doggone well
what I'm talking about.
You've been
sleeping with my wife.
I found this under the bed.
What a breakthrough.
- Alan...
- What?
You finally confronted the rage
you have against your father.
Oh, come on.
And even in this bizarre
situation, you are expressing it.
- Bravo.
- You've been sleeping with my wife.
This calls for a
private session.
Well, you got that right.
Uh, Tues... No,
Tuesday is no good.
- Thursday, 6:30 p.m.?
- Yeah, 6:30.
Yeah. Here. I hope
you get cancer.
That's good. That is very good.
Anger. Anger.
Now, this is what
I want you to do...
Hold on to that thought
until I see you Thursday.
- But...
- Okay?
Now...
Next Wednesday, we'll begin
divorce counseling, hmm?
Marshall...
Hi.
Wait.
Alan, you're early.
Oh, no.
Now, now, wait a
minute. Just take it easy.
Hey!
What's going on?
It doesn't look too
good for me, does it?
You came flying out of an office
where a man has just been murdered
and then ran from
the security guard.
Could be worse,
but I don't know how.
What about that guy that
was there just after me?
Maybe he killed Fletcher.
Fellow named Turner.
The guard already verified that
Dr. Fletcher was alive when left.
So I guess I'm the main suspect.
You're the only suspect, Alan.
Look at this arrest report.
What?
They read you your rights, told
you you didn't have to say anything,
told you that whatever you
said would be used against you.
Yeah, I remember that.
The officer even asked me if I
understood what he was saying.
That's because he couldn't
believe what you were saying.
You told him that Dr. Fletcher
was having an affair with your wife
and you burst into his office
furious and had words with him.
And now they're using
what you said against you.
I don't know
why I said all that.
Alan, your mouth
is a big problem.
Just when I'm nervous.
You're nervous 25 hours a day.
Why did you panic and run?
When I saw Dr. Fletcher dead,
I remembered this insurance
seminar on break-ins
where it was pointed out that
after the scene of a shooting
the culprit is often
still lying in wait.
I remember this clearly because it
was either late May or early June of '87...
Maybe it was '88... but it was
right after I was named Salesman...
Alan.
Who was there when you
burst into the doctor's office?
A couple in session and a
woman in the waiting room.
And they're the only ones who knew that
you were coming back on Thursday at 6:30?
Yeah... and Laura.
You told Laura?
You're not going to
take my case, are you?
Boy, I don't want to. Mm-mm.
But I guess I will.
You will?
Yeah. As aggravating as you are,
you couldn't kill anybody
unless you bored them to death.
I'll make bail.
How are you going to pay me?
Oh, I don't know.
Uh, selling insurance policies.
It will take a car load.
Alan.
I was worried about you.
Thanks for posting bail.
You could have just
sent some tobacco over.
Alan, I know you're upset.
It's okay if you take it out on me.
- Well, that's hostile.
- You're hostile.
- I'm not hostile.
- Hold it. Hold it. Hold it.
- All I said was...
- I know what you said.
- Hold it!
- I'm hurt, but I'm not hostile.
Hold it!
What's the matter with you?
About to go on trial for murder
and all you can think about
is being hurt and hostile
and fighting with your wife.
- Now stop it.
- But I... Stop it!
I want to ask you
some questions alone.
- But...
- Alone.
Okay.
I'm not hostile.
I'm hurt, but I'm not hostile.
Did you have an affair
with Harding Fletcher?
No.
Of course, you wouldn't
tell me if you did.
Of course I would.
You're Alan's lawyer. I can't
help Alan if I don't tell you the truth.
You want to help Alan?
Of course.
My relationship with Harding
Fletcher was strictly professional.
He was a wonderful therapist...
Warm and caring and empathetic.
Alan doesn't share your opinion.
I was at a "for wives only" seminar
at the clinic the night Harding died.
You should have seen
the outpouring of feelings.
It was... amazing.
Hmm.
Anything else?
Yeah. Be nice to Alan.
No yelling, no fighting
till this thing's over.
I understand.
Alan arrested for murder.
He's under a terrible strain.
I'll be very supportive,
Mr. Matlock.
He needs to concentrate
on what's important.
His trial.
Yeah, his trial.
And insurance.
He needs to sell
insurance, a lot of insurance.
Why didn't anybody
hear the shots?
All the rooms in the
clinic are sound-proofed.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
Well, you know, these people
paid this Dr. Fletcher a lot of money
to have him listen to
them scream at each other.
That's how they worked
out their differences.
- Do you believe that?
- I don't know.
You know, my parents did that.
Yeah, they'd have a fight,
and he'd slam out the door,
and an hour later he'd be back
bringing her some ice cream.
Who needs a doctor, right?
- I guess that makes sense.
- Yeah.
You know, Dr. Fletcher
had a lot of patients.
Where are his
files and his notes?
Well, we didn't find
any... not one note.
Hmm.
No notes?
No, no, no.
Dr. Relkin?
I'm Ben Matlock.
Oh, yes.
You're Alan Corning's attorney.
How may I help you?
Tell him to stop that.
See you on Thursday, Fred.
Sorry. They think you're a new patient,
and they're welcoming you to the group.
No, I don't think I'd fit in.
I just want to ask a
couple of questions.
You heard that Alan Corning
broke into Dr. Fletcher's office
a few days before the murder?
Everyone knew about that.
I understand there was a couple in
session and a woman in the waiting room.
Would you happen
to know who they are?
I should. I keep a master
appointment list for billing purposes.
Let's see...
Dr. Fletcher's patients.
Here.
The couple in session were
the Morells... Ginny and Joe.
And the next patient... the woman in
the waiting room... was Claudette Hertz.
See, the Morells and Mrs.
Hertz are scheduled today.
Uh-huh.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
I'm looking for Joe
and Ginny Morell!
I'm Ginny Morell.
Is this...
Is this a martial arts class?
No, this is therapy.
I heard that you and
your husband knew
that Alan Corning was going
to be in Dr. Fletcher's office
at 6:30 the night of the murder.
Correct?
Yes, okay?
We knew that he had an
appointment with Dr. Fletcher.
If we'd only known that he
was going to murder Dr. Fletcher,
Joe would have
never gone out of town.
I would not have gone to
the "for wives only" seminar.
I mean, Dr. Fletcher saved
our marriage, Mr. Matlock,
and I don't know what
we're going to do without him.
Well, maybe you'll find
another Dr. Fletcher.
No. There's only
one Dr. Fletcher.
Well, just keep
plenty of these things
and just kick the living...
you know... Out of them.
It's like the Marx Brothers.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
What's the matter?
I'm screaming.
I know.
It's primal screaming.
Oh. Oh, oh.
Does your husband
scream with you?
My husband's gone.
I'm sorry. How old was he?
He's not dead. We're divorcing.
Aah! Aah!
Dr. Fletcher showed us that we
didn't belong together, so we parted.
Aah! Aah!
But Dr. Fletcher stood by me.
He gave me strength,
support, self-esteem.
Good.
I have to ask you...
- No, don't do that.
- I have to.
- No, you can't!
- I must!
- I have to ask you where you were...
- Aah!
- No. No.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I
don't mean to upset you.
Waah!
Will you stop screaming?
You're starting to hurt my throat!
I was at the "wives
only" seminar.
Aah! Aah!
You have a lovely scream.
Thank you for sharing.
Aah!
Ben, I just got to
Dr. Fletcher's house.
Yeah, I'll let you
know what I find.
Goodbye.
When I got to Dr. Fletcher's house,
I knew someone was already there.
And sure enough,
out comes this blonde
carrying a leather and rhinestone
jacket and a diamond bracelet.
- Blonde, huh?
- Yeah.
Yea tall, beautiful,
hair cut to about here.
That's Laura... Alan's wife.
Right.
So then I followed her
to this fancy apartment
where this great-looking
brunette comes to the door.
Kind of curly?
Yeah.
That's Claudette
Hertz. Then what?
Then the tall blonde gave the
diamond bracelet to the curly brunette.
- Then what?
- That's it.
Now what?
Uh... I like to talk to blondes.
How did you know I was
at Dr. Fletcher's house?
You were having me followed.
Well, certainly.
What was going on
between you and Dr. Fletcher?
I already told you... nothing.
I don't believe you.
Then why don't you tell me?
I think you and Dr. Fletcher
were having an affair
and you took incriminating
evidence from his house...
The jacket and the bracelet.
I'm not talking to
you, Mr. Matlock.
Then I'll just talk
to your husband.
You would tell Alan?
Well, certainly.
I have to be honest with
him, and Alan already knows.
All right.
I was having an affair
with Harding Fletcher.
I was feeling alienated and vulnerable,
and Harding had a need to nurture.
Do you understand?
Sure. You were
hot for each other.
The affair was a mistake.
I love Alan.
I wouldn't want to hurt him, so I went
to Harding's place and got my things.
You took a jacket and
a bracelet from his place
and then went to Claudette Hertz'
apartment and gave her the bracelet.
Why would you do that?
Claudette's a
dear friend of mine,
and the bracelet had sad
memories for me, so I gave it to her.
Well, if you and Claudette
are such dear friends,
why didn't Alan recognize
her in the waiting room?
Claudette and I became
friends at a women's group.
Alan never met her.
Okay.
I know you have to defend him,
but you don't have to cause
him any additional pain.
You don't have to tell him.
Well, Alan...
Well, we'll see.
Here you go.
Hmm. Oh, thank you.
Oh, that's a beautiful bracelet.
Yes, it is.
Nice of Laura to give it to you.
How many carats?
Five-something.
Women don't give other
women $10,000 bracelets.
Actually, she just
loaned it to me.
Oh.
Well, that doesn't
make sense, either.
I mean, if she didn't want to wear
it or even look at it, it's too valuable.
She would have put it away
or... Like in a safety deposit box.
Uh, unless it's yours.
What are you talking about?
Well, suppose you left that
bracelet at Dr. Fletcher's house,
and Laura picked it up for you
when she went to get her jacket.
I've never been to
Dr. Fletcher's house,
and I resent the insinuation.
Well, I'm sure you do.
But when things don't
make sense to me...
Like Laura giving you that
bracelet or loaning it to you...
Then my mind goes to
explanations that do make sense.
I'll show you out, Mr. Matlock.
Okay.
Oh, that's a shame.
Something wrong?
I've got a carpet cleaner that
can lift that right out of your rug.
I've already called one.
Oh, good.
Have a nice day.
Laura Corning and Claudette
Hertz both lied to me.
- Both of them?
- Yeah.
Laura Corning had an
affair with Dr. Fletcher.
Oh.
Alan's wife was having an affair
with their marriage counselor?
Yeah. And I'm sure that Claudette
Hertz did, too, but she wouldn't admit it.
Wow.
Dr. Fletcher knew about
what comes naturally.
Yeah. He was giving out a little
more than advice, wasn't he?
So I guess one of the
ladies figured it out and...
Think that's what happened?
They both lied to me,
Conrad, about everything.
So I think they lied
about their alibis.
Doing what comes
naturally with two?
Put a man on thin ice.
Yeah.
How about tomorrow we stop by
that marriage counseling place?
So good to see you, Mr. Matlock.
Conrad, this is Dr. Relkin.
You're no stranger to hugging.
No, I'm not.
Everybody in my family hugs
everybody else all the time.
How healthy. How wonderful.
Has your family always hugged,
or was there a significant event
that precipitated the behavior?
Well, let me see...
While Conrad tries to remember,
I'd like to ask some questions.
Laura Corning and
Claudette Hertz have said
that they were in your
"for wives only" seminar
at the time Dr. Fletcher
was murdered.
Is that your recollection?
That seminar was packed.
I was worried I hadn't mimeoed
enough questionnaires to go around,
but I definitely remember
seeing Claudette and Laura there.
If you gentlemen will excuse
me, I have to start a group session.
Oh, Doctor, we always hugged.
- Good.
- Yeah.
Good.
Very good.
See, Ben, hugging is
why I grew up to be so nice.
You'd fit right in here.
- There's the jacket.
- What jacket?
That's the jacket I saw Laura
Corning carry from Dr. Fletcher's house.
That's Ginny Morell.
That makes three of them.
- Three?
- Yeah.
Give me a minute.
You're wearing
Laura Corning's jacket.
It's my jacket.
Laura told me she left that
jacket at Dr. Fletcher's house.
I loaned it to Laura before
Dr. Fletcher was murdered.
You're sure you didn't
leave it there yourself?
Hey, look, I spent four
years and $50,000 in therapy
because my father was
a nosy old coot like you.
So I'm not answering any more of
your questions, Pops... like it or lump it.
Move. I'm late for
my sensitivity class.
Hi.
Hi yourself.
How did it go?
That woman you were so
nice to just called me Pops.
That's awful.
That's just awful, Pops.
I think that is her jacket, and I think
she left it in Dr. Fletcher's house.
You really think he was
having affairs with three women?
Laura said he was nurturing.
I think he nurtured
like a big bunny rabbit.
One of them killed him.
Maybe each of them
found out about the others.
Yeah.
A woman scorned...
More than that...
Three patients scorned and
manipulated in a very unethical way
by a doctor who has
sworn to try to help them.
And all this jerk
did was use them.
Doing what comes naturally.
He did it a little
too well, didn't he?
We've been over
this place three times.
We're not going
to find those notes.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
We might as well go.
I've got a feeling those
notes would make all the...
All the difference.
- Wait.
- Wait a minute.
There's Dr. Fletcher
in his office.
Mrs. Morell, you and your husband were
in marriage counseling with Dr. Fletcher.
Correct?
Yes, we were.
And you also saw him alone?
No, only with Joe.
You never once went
alone to his house?
No, of course not.
Do you deny that you left an
expensive jacket at his house?
I never left any jacket
because I was never there.
Do you deny the
jacket was there?
Well, no. I loaned the
jacket to somebody.
I can only assume
that she left it there.
Oh. Uh, Laura Corning?
- Yes.
- Uh-huh.
Uh, Mrs. Morell, is, uh...
is this your jacket?
Yes.
It's very beautiful.
Very... Very expensive.
Look at that. Mmm.
What size would you say it is?
Oh, it's right here on
the label, size 6 petite.
You're a very small
woman, aren't you?
- Petite.
- Of course.
You say you loaned this
jacket to Laura Corning?
Yes.
Is Mrs. Corning in
the courtroom today?
Yes.
Would you point her out, please?
Mrs. Corning, would
you please stand up?
Huh.
Thank you.
Mrs. Corning is a fairly tall
lady, a little larger than you.
Why would she borrow a
jacket that was too small for her?
I don't know.
Mrs. Corning didn't
wear this jacket
and didn't leave it at Dr. Fletcher's
house. You must have.
You were there, and you
left the jacket, didn't you?
Objection. Your
Honor, this is irrelevant.
Sustained. Mr. Matlock...
But, Your Honor...
Objection sustained.
Now please move on.
No further questions.
Mrs. Corning, you and your
husband were in marriage counseling
with the late Dr. Fletcher,
is that correct?
Yes.
And at the same time,
you were having an affair with
the late Dr. Fletcher, weren't you?
Yes.
And when you found out that
Ginny Morell and Claudette Hertz
were also having affairs
with the late Dr. Fletcher,
did that make you feel
angry and deceived?
I don't know anything
about Ginny or Claudette,
but if you're saying I got jealous
and killed him, I have witnesses.
Oh, I know. You were at
the "for wives only" seminar.
But sometime after that,
didn't you break into Dr. Fletcher's
house and remove a jacket and a bracelet?
I didn't break in. I had a key.
I don't get it.
You had a key.
You let yourself into Dr. Fletcher's
house after the murder
and removed a jacket
belonging to Mrs. Morell
and an expensive bracelet
belonging to Claudette Hertz.
Why would you risk going back
into that house after the murder
to remove evidence that obviously
incriminated people other than yourself?
Well, I wasn't sure that I had all
of my things out of there or not,
and so, when I
discovered that I had,
I found Ginny's jacket
and Claudette's bracelet.
Well, they're very
dear friends of mine.
I don't think either one of them
had an affair with Dr. Fletcher.
And so I decided to remove
their things, you know,
so they wouldn't be compromised.
I see... I...
I think.
But, uh... Well,
nothing further.
Mrs. Hertz, did you leave a diamond
bracelet at Dr. Fletcher's house?
You know I did.
Laura Corning says that she
removed that bracelet from his house
so that you wouldn't
be compromised.
She said she did it out of her
deep and everlasting friendship
with you and Ginny
Morell. Is that true?
Yes. The three of
us are very close.
Well, you had a lot in common.
You were all having
marital problems,
you were all in the clinic,
and you were all having affairs
with Dr. Fletcher, weren't you?
That's a lie.
You didn't know of one
another's affairs with him
until the morning Alan Corning
came bursting into the office,
yelling at the good doctor
for fooling around with his wife.
That's the day that you
and Ginny Morell found out
the doctor had been
cheating on you, wasn't it?
That's absurd.
Did you feel a little angry when
you found out you'd been deceived?
I'm not stupid, Mr. Matlock. I
know what you're leading up to.
I did not kill Dr. Fletcher.
- I was at the "wives only" seminar.
- "Wives only" seminar.
Yeah, yeah.
The three of you are each other's
witnesses, but somebody's lying.
Objection. Counsel has ceased
asking questions and begun ruminating.
Uh, Your Honor, the
questions are coming, I promise.
- They're coming, Your Honor.
- Well, let's hear them, then, Mr. Matlock.
- Objection overruled.
- Thank you.
Who could be lying?
Who killed Dr. Fletcher?
And it took me a
while to figure it out,
but I finally realized the
only way I could know
was to find Dr. Fletcher's
personal notes.
Now, do you have any idea what
happened to those personal notes?
None at all.
Neither does anybody
else, seemingly.
I looked for them and looked for them and
looked for them, and I couldn't find them.
But I finally... I finally figured
out where they had been...
In a safe in
Dr. Fletcher's office.
Now, do you know
where that safe turned up?
- I have no idea.
- Huh.
It was in your
apartment, wasn't it?
That's ridiculous. There's
no safe in my apartment.
No, no, no.
There's no safe in
your apartment now.
It was. Not now.
Now it's here.
Uh, thank you, Mr. McMasters.
Your Honor, could we mark
this safe Defense Exhibit C?
Is this the safe that
was in your apartment?
I never saw it before.
And you were in my apartment.
You didn't see it there, either.
No, I didn't. I didn't.
But I know it had been in there.
You know how I know?
By the rust indentations
on your brand-new rug.
I got to thinking, here you are in
a new apartment with a new rug,
and yet something had
already been moved out.
Now, how did those rust
indentations get in your rug?
I don't know.
Dr. Fletcher had the
same rust indentations...
on a rug in the corner...
of his office. You see there?
See that? See that?
Let's see, let's mark this
picture Defense Exhibit D.
It was hanging in
Dr. Fletcher's office.
See, this is a picture
of Dr. Fletcher,
his office furniture,
including the safe... see?
There.
Now, let's mark this
photo Defense Exhibit E,
taken at the scene of
the crime after the murder.
Now see? Same
office furniture, no safe.
See? No safe.
What happened to
the safe, Mrs. Hertz?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Your building superintendent,
Mr. Anthony Giarelli,
you do remember
slipping him $100
to get that safe out of
your apartment in a hurry
the day you found out I was
coming out for a visit, don't you?
No.
Laura Corning called you
and told you, didn't she?
Absolutely not.
If I told you that Mr. Giarelli's
in the courtroom today,
would that improve
your recollection?
Would you stand
up, Mr. Giarelli?
Now do you remember?
It's not what you think.
You don't know what
I think, so I'll tell you.
I think you, Ginny Morell,
Laura Corning got together
and realized that Dr. Fletcher
had probably kept notes
on his affairs with you.
Now, Ginny Morell and Laura Corning
have husbands. That's bad enough.
But you're being divorced,
looking for a nice settlement.
When word of your
adultery got out,
that would hurt your cause
pretty good, wouldn't it?
I am still in the
middle of a divorce.
I know. I know. I know.
You have the most to lose.
That's why I think
you killed Dr. Fletcher.
You wanted to
destroy those files,
but you didn't have time
to open the safe there,
so you took the safe
to your apartment,
got it opened, and
destroyed the files, didn't you?
No, I told you, I was
at the "wives only"...
"Wives only" seminar.
I know. I know.
You were there for
a while, but you left.
When everybody came back
after coffee break at the seminar...
Dr. Relkin passed out
these questionnaires.
Everybody filled them
out and signed them.
Your name appears nowhere
on these questionnaires.
Why?
Dr. Relkin must have lost it.
Miss Powell, you can
remove the safe now.
Dr. Relkin told me that she picked up
and numbered all of these questionnaires.
Why isn't your name on here?
Well, how should I know? It
could have fallen on the floor.
Oh, I'm sorry, Miss Powell.
You need help. Could you...
Officer?
That's interesting.
Excuse me.
It takes not one, not two, but
three women to move that safe.
You can put it down
now, thank you.
You couldn't possibly have moved
that safe by yourself, could you?
It took three women
to move that safe.
Dr. Fletcher was
shot three times.
Three women killed him: you,
Ginny Morell, Laura Corning.
- Your Honor...
- Besides your questionnaire,
two other questionnaires are missing...
Ginny Morell and Laura Corning.
You left early, didn't you?
Went over to Dr. Fletcher's, killed
him, and then you removed the safe.
Objection, Your Honor.
- Mr. Matlock.
- One more question.
Are you going to take the
blame for this murder alone,
or are you going to admit that
what I just said really happened?
It's up to you, Mrs. Hertz.
I can't thank you enough, Ben.
Just keep selling insurance.
Well, I can't for a while.
Why the hell not?
You've got to understand, Ben, my
wife was deceiving me with our therapist,
and I've been tried for
murder, and she did it.
My new therapist says that anyone
else would be dead from the stress,
- and I will be, too, if I don't...
- What?
Go away for a while,
a long while. Nature.
Don't get me wrong,
Ben, I'll pay you.
Good.
It may take me years,
maybe the rest of my life.
The rest of your life?
Ben, people are living
longer and longer.
I was at a seminar last
year... Wait, two years ago...
It was in June...
no wait, July...
And they said that men
are living into their 90s...
Wait, wait... women are living
into their 90s and men into their 80s.
You know, a nonsmoker like
you, well, then, you know...
www.tvsubtitles.net